Guide to the Owen Dodson Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Owen Dodson collection
1896-1982
1936-1982
JWJ MSS 103
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
7.1
(19 boxes)
Dodson, Owen, 1914-1983
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired by gift and purchase from various sources. For further information, see notes at the level of each acquisition.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Owen Dodson (1914-1983)
Owen Vincent Dodson, American playwright, was born in Brooklyn, New York in 1914. He received a B.A. from Bates College in 1936 and a M.F.A. in playwriting from the Yale School of Drama in 1939. He was on the faculty of Howard University's Drama Department from 1947 to 1969. He also briefly worked for Spelman College, Atlanta University, and Hampton Institute. Although best known for his playwriting, Dodson also published two novels and several volumes of poetry.
Scope and Contents
The Owen Dodson Collection consists of correspondence, writings, diaries, photographs, artwork, and posters that document the life and work of American playwright and poet Owen Dodson. The bulk of the material was created and accumulated by Owen Dodson in the course of his activities as an author and theater director, though portions of the collection were acquired from other sources.
Arrangement
Organized into two groupings: Acquisitions before 1994; May 1994 and June 1995 Acquisitions.
African American authors -- 20th Century -- Archives; African American dramatists -- 20th Century -- Archives; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Dramatists, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Diaries; Photographs; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Dramatists -- United States -- 20th Century; Dodson, Owen, 1914-1983
- Acquisitions before 1994, 1936-1951; Series I; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Organized into four series: I. Correspondence, 1937-1945. II. Writings, 1936-1951. III. Personal Papers, 1942. IV. Drawings, undated.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Material in this grouping was chiefly acquired by gift from Owen Dodson, 1939-1945, and dates unknown.
  - Correspondence, 1937-1945; Series I
    - General correspondence, A-Z, 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      To: 1 / From: 15
    - Anderson, Margaret, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      To: 3 / From: 0
    - Auden, W. H., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
      To: 1 / From: 0
    - Bond, J. Max, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      To: 2 / From: 0
    - Buck, Pearl S., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Crawford, George W., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cullen, Countee, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      To: 4 / From: 0
    - Dodson, Kenneth, 1938 October (Box 1, Folder 8)
      To: 0 / From: 1
    - [Dodson], Lil, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - DuBois, William E. B., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Ellison, Ralph, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Embree, Edwin R., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Frederick, John T., 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Horne, Lena, 1945 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      To: 0 / From: 1 (copy)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1944 February (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Jackman, Harold, 1937, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      To: 0 / From: 2
    - Johnson, Charles S., 1944 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Greer, 1943 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - MacLeish, Mrs. Andrew, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Includes letter to Archibald MacLeish from Margaret Anderson (enclosure)
    - Mauriber, Saul, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Negro Freedom Rally, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Includes letters signed by Adam Clayton Powell, Jr.
    - Patterson, Frederick D., 1941 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr.
      Related Archival Materials note
      See: Negro Freedom Rally
    - Prophet, N. Elizabeth, 1943 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Sebree, Charles, 1942 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      From Alexander Brooks to Charles Sebree
    - Theatre Arts, 1943-1944 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Includes: "Principal Themes from China"
      To: 13 / From: 0
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1939-1943, undated (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
      To: 3 / From: 6
    - Voorhees, Lillian W., 1939 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Writings, 1936-1951; Series II
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Americus, Ga. [poem]
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Amistad [play]
      - Second draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Notes with unidentified comments, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - The Ballad of Dorie Miller
      - Drafts, autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, with mimeograph copy, 1943, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Bayou Legend [play]
      - Mimeograph copy, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Black Mother Praying in the Summer
      - Drafts, autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, 1943, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Boy at the Window
      - Organizational notes, circa 1946-1951 (Box 1, Folder 35-36)
      - Organizational notes, circa 1946-1951 (Box 2, Folder 37-39)
      - Early draft of chapter 1, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - "Some first drafts," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 2, Folder 41-42)
      - "A draft for the typist," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 2, Folder 43-44)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, undated (Box 2, Folder 45-47)
    - The Carter Family [film treatment]
      - Typescript carbon, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - [Christmas Poem]
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, 1942 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Divine Comedy
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 50-51)
      - Libretto and score, autograph manuscript, photostat, 1938? (Box 3, Folder 51a)
      - Typescript carbon, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 51b)
        [Includes printed copy of poem: "Laughter Underneath the Rock" in envelope addressed to Mr. and Mrs. Norman DeMarco, 1946 December 22]
    - Doomsday Tale
      - "First notes," autograph manuscript, corrected, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - First draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Everybody Join Hands
      - "2nd draft," autograph manuscript, corrected, accompanied by notes, mimeograph of script, and program, [1943] (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Freedom the Banner
      - "Rough draft," autograph manuscript, corrected, accompanied by notes, mimeograph of script, and program, [1943] (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - The Garden of Time
      - Notes, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Outline with draft pages, 1939, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - "2nd draft," autograph manuscript, corrected, 1938 December (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - "1st rewrites," typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - "Rewrite of 2nd Draft," typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - The Graveyard and the Circus
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Heroes on Parade
      - Mimeograph script, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Hotspots U.S.A.
      - Mimeograph script, 1945 January 7 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Including Laughter [play]
      - Typescript, corrected, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Jonathan's Song [poem]
      - Drafts, autograph manuscript and typescript carbon, corrected, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - "Laughter Underneath the Rock"
      See: Divine Comedy, Box 3, folder 51b
    - New World A-Coming
      Pageant for the second Negro Freedom Rally.
      - Notes, 1944, undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - "1st Draft," autograph manuscript, corrected, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - "2nd Draft," autograph manuscript, corrected, 1944 May (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - "2nd Draft Corrected," typescript, 1944 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - "2nd Draft corrected again," typescript carbon, [1944] (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - "Final version," mimeograph script, [1944] (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - [Poems written at Bates College]
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Preparing for Miracles [story]
      - Typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
        Includes: letter from Margarita Smith of Mademoiselle
    - "Ruby May Counts: Blue Singer" [poem]
      - Autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Soundtrack for a Dance
      - Typescript, carbon, [1944] (Box 4, Folder 74a)
    - The Southern Star [play]
      - Autograph manuscript, corrected, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - The Third Fourth of July
      Ballet written with Countee Cullen
      - "2nd draft," typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - A Tropical Fable [musical]
      - Program, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - "Two Metaphors for Carl Van Vechten" [poem]
      - Autograph manuscript, 1943 January (Box 4, Folder 77a)
  - Personal Papers, 1942; Series III
    - "Godspeed and Bon Voyage from the Communications Center and the People of Pygmalion", 1942 October (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Drawings, Series IV
    - Costume designs for Countee Cullen's Medea, ten drawings, undated (Box 19, Folder 241)
- May 1994 and June 1995 Acquisitions, 1896-1982; Series II; 5.25; (13 boxes)
  Organized into seven series: I. Correspondence, 1896-1981. II. Writings, 1941-1982. III. Diaries, 1938-1982. IV. Photographs, 1951-1977. V. Posters, 1947-1977. VI. Drawings, 1947-1964. VII. Papers Relating to the Estate of Edith Dodson, 1963-1983.
  Purchased from McBlain Books on the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts & Letters Fund, 1994-1995.
  - Correspondence, 1896-1981; Series I; 0.42; (1 box)
    Organized into two subseries: Owen Dodson Correspondence, and Family Correspondence.
    - Owen Dodson Correspondence
      Arranged alphabetically.
      - Arbita, Malcolm, 1979 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - Bethea, Ednah, 1943-1983 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Brown, William T., 1964 May 17 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Cleaveland, Henry Folger, 1977 July 9 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Copyright Office (Library of Congress), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Dodson, Edith, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - Embree, Edwin R., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Fenton, Edward, circa 1957-1965 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Foster, Elizabeth, undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Gorer, Geoffrey, 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 87b)
      - Hardy, Sallee, 1978, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Hodgson, Jane, undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Hospitalized Veterans Writing Project, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Olson, Jery and BoBo, 1956 June 13, undated (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - The Paris Review, 1956 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Phi Beta Kappa Society, Howard University, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - Pinnacle Books, Inc., 1982 (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Priebe, Karl, circa 1947-1976 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Read, Florence, 1961, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Robinson, Albert, 1945 July 9 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - Shine, Ted, 1981 September 29 (Box 5, Folder 98)
      - Smith, Abbott P., 1951 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - Unthank, Thomas, 1980 January 15, February 11 (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, 1944-1962 (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - Yaddo, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - General correspondence, 1949-1983 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Family Correspondence
      - Dodson, Edith incoming, 1954-1981
        - Brown, Robert, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 104)
        - Fabre, Genevieve, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 105)
        - Forsyth, Louise, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 106)
        - Pool, Rosey E., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 107)
        - General, 1964-1981 (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - Dodson, Owen to Edith Dodson, circa 1954-1970 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - Dodson, Kenneth, to Dodson sisters, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - [Dodson], Nathaniel to Sarah [Dodson], Brooklyn NY, 1896 February 13 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Writings, 1941-1982; Series II; 2.09; (5 boxes)
    Organized into two subseries: Writings of Owen Dodson, and Writings of Others.
    - Writings of Owen Dodson
      - Africa Where I Baked My Bread, review by Lance Jeffers, draft, autograph manuscript, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 112)
      - "Black Breakthrough," proposals and related correspondence, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 113)
        The proposed book was to have been a volume of portraits by Carl Van Vechten accompanied by text by Owen Dodson.
      - Come Home Early, Child (novel), draft, typescript, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 114)
      - The Confession Stone: Song Cycles
        - Printed copy, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 115)
          Removed from frame
        - Printed copies, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 116)
        - Draft, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - The Crisis, book review, draft, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - The Divine Comedy, draft, typescript (copy), undated (Box 6, Folder 119-120)
      - The Harlem Book of the Dead, reviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 121)
      - I Saw How Black I was (introduction to an anthology of poetry), draft, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
      - Memories of Rosey Pool (Box 6, Folder 123)
      - Who Has Seen the Wind, draft, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 124)
      - "The Widows Walk," "My Love is Tender of the Holy Crosses," and "Ballad of Badmen" (poems), drafts, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
      - Unidentified, notes, typescript and autograph manuscript, undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Writings of Others
      Arranged alphabetically by author.
      - Adler, Marnie: poems, typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
      - Barbour, Floyd
        - Antony and Cleopatra (play), draft, typescript, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 128)
        - Auto Sacramental (play), draft, typescript, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 129)
        - The Bird Cage (play), draft, typescript, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 130)
        - Captain America (play), draft, typescript, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 131)
        - ESSO (play), draft, typescript, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 132)
        - The Firefly Arcade (play), draft, typescript, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 133)
        - GATES to ANY KINGDOM (play), draft, typescript, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 134)
      - Brown, Kevin: The Prophecy of Sebastian (novel), typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 135)
      - Chambers, Chico
        - One Sunday Mawnin', the old man screamed!... I'ma Build Me A Mountain So's My Children Can Dream (play), typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 136)
        - "Spinners of Soft Black Birth-songs" (poem), typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 137)
      - Davis, Ossie: Curtain Call, Mr. Aldrige Sir, (dramatic reading), typescript, 1963 January 28 (Box 7, Folder 138)
      - Dean, Phillip Hayes: Everynight when the Sun Goes Down typescript, draft, copy, undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
      - Fudge, Anthony R.: Egghead Thorough (poems), typescript, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 140)
      - Greenlee, Sam: Blues for Little Prez and South Side Blues: A Jazz Love Poem in Two Acts (plays), typescript, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 141)
      - Haines, Corrie: "Your Servant: Judas" (poem), typescript, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 142)
      - Jeffers, Lance: Untitled poem, typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 143)
      - Lee, Ritten Edward: Cush draft, typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 144)
      - Liyong, Taban lo: Apwoyo Gin Ki Lyec (fable), typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 145)
      - Matheus, John: Tambour (play), typescript, copy of a 1929 original, undated (Box 8, Folder 146)
      - Norman, Riley
        - The Black Panther (play), typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 147-148)
        - Runaway People (play), typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 149)
        - Untitled prose draft, typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 150)
      - Shine, Theodis
        - Cold Day in August (play), typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 151)
        - Idabel's Fortune (play), typescript, two copies, undated (Box 8, Folder 152)
        - Morning, Noon, and Night (play), typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 153)
      - Wesley, Richard
        - Gettin' it Together (play), typescript, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 154)
        - The Last Street Play (play), typescript, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 155)
        - The Past is Past (play), typescript, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 156)
        - Strike Heaven on the Face (play), typescript, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 157)
      - Wiggins, Ernest: "Play Street" (poem), typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 158)
      - Unidentified author: Cotton Patch (play), typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - Personal Papers, 1934-1982; Series III; 1.25; (3 boxes)
    - Clippings relating to Owen Dodson, circa 1952 (Box 9, Folder 160)
    - Diaries, 1934-1939 (Box 9, Folder 161-165)
    - Diaries, 1942, undated (Box 10, Folder 166-167)
    - Desk Diaries, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 168-172)
    - The Lion, yearbook of Lincoln Univeristy, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - The Garnet, Bates College, 1937 June (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Printed material and correspondence relating to Bates College and Howard University, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Theater programs and related ephemera, 1951-1982 (Box 11, Folder 176-179)
    - "Ten Master Painters" announcement, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 180)
    - Notes and ephemera, 1937-1983 (Box 12, Folder 181-182)
    - Clippings, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 183)
    - Curriculum vitae of Owen Dodson, 1959-1979 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Photographs, 1951-1977; Series IV; 1.25; (3 boxes)
    - [_____, Eleanora?], undated (Box 13, Folder 181a)
    - [Priebe, Karl?], undated (Box 13, Folder 182a)
    - Jackson, Harold, photographs, undated
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, photograph, undated
    - Dodson, Owen and Edith, photographs and negatives, 1951-1977 (Box 13, Folder 185-191)
      Other subjects include Georgia Douglass Johnson, James Moore, Beverly and Karia Bryn Robeson Kelch, Eleanor Traylor, Athur Taylor, and others.
    - Dodson, Owen and Edith, photographs and negatives, 1951-1977 (Box 14, Folder 192-200)
    - Photographs and correspondence relating to Darryl Croxton, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 201)
    - Photographs and negatives of a house and wedding, 1960-1967 (Box 14, Folder 202-205)
    - Photographs and negatives of a house and wedding, 1960-1967 (Box 15, Folder 206-210)
    - Promotional keychain slide viewer for Oedipus Rex, undated (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Posters, 1947-1979; Series V
    - Bayou Legend, undated
    - The Confession Stone, 1979
    - Defiant Island, undated
    - Dr. Faustus (Howard University Players), undated
    - Dutchman and Sho is Hot in the Cotton Patch, undated
    - Garden of Time, undated
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night, undated
    - Macbeth, accompanied by a note from Edmund Cambridge, 1977
    - Medea in Africa (Howard University Players), 1963
    - The Mighty Gents, accompanied by a note from Richard Wesley, undated
    - Oedipus Rex (Howard University Players), 1966
    - You Can't Take It With You (Howard University Players), 1966
    - Three one-act plays of the absurd, 1966
    - Unidentified, undated
  - Drawings, Series VI
    - Unidentified, pen and ink, unidentified artist, 1964
    - "Play within the play scene," pen and ink, unidentified artist, 1964
    - Portrait of Owen Dodson, charcoal, unidentified artist, undated
    - "He hasn't read Kafka!," pen and ink, by Barrett, 1947
    - Untitled, pen and ink, by Gregory, 1964
    - "Darmon Braswell as Claudius," by Gregory, 1964
    - "Hamlet," by Gregory, 1964
  - Papers Relating to the Estate of Edith Dodson, 1963-1983; Series VII; 0.83; (2 boxes)
    - Bills and correspondence relating to the estate of Edith Dodson, 1963-1983 (Box 16, Folder 212-215)
    - Bills and correspondence relating to the estate of Edith Dodson, 1963-1983 (Box 17, Folder 216-217)
  - Oversize, 0.25; (1 box)
    - Jackson, Harold (Series IV), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 218)
    - The Importance of Being Ernest (Series IV), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 219)
    - Bayou Legend (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 220)
    - The Confession Stone (Series V), 1979 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 221)
    - Defiant Island (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Overize), Folder 222)
    - Dr. Faustus (Howard University Players) (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 223)
    - Dutchman and Sho is Hot in the Cotton Patch (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 224)
    - Garden of Time (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 225)
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 226)
    - Macbeth, accompanied by a note from Edmund Cambridge (Series V), 1977 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 227)
    - Medea in Africa (Howard University Players) (Series V), 1963 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 228)
    - The Mighty Gents accompanied by a note from Richard Wesley (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 229)
    - Oedipus Rex (Howard University Players) (Series V), 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 230)
    - You Can't Take it with You (Howard University Players) (Series V), 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 231)
    - Three one-act plays of the absurd (Series V), 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 232)
    - Unidentified (Series V), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 233)
    - Untitled, pen and ink, unidentified artist (Series VI), 1964 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 234)
    - "Play within the play scene," pen and ink, unidentified artist (Series VI), 1964 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 235)
    - Portrait of Owen Dodson, charcoal, unidentified artist (Series VI), undated (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 236)
    - "He hasn't read Kafka!," pen and ink, by Barrett (Series VI), 1947 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 237)
    - Untitled, pen and ink, by Gregory (Series VI), 1964 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 238)
    - "Darmon Braswell as Claudius," by Gregory (Series VI), 1964 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 239)
    - "Hamlet," by Gregory (Series VI), 1964 (Box 18 (Oversize), Folder 240)